Welcome to the Western India Review channel.
Let's take a look at the top five best car
insurance companies available in India.
If you're new to the channel,
please subscribe,
like the video, and mention in the comments which car
insurance company you prefer.
Let's take a look at
number five: Royal
Sundaram General Insurance Company. The parent company of this company is
Sundaram Finance Limited.
Its headquarters is located in Chennai.
This company was started in 2001. It provides
excellent insurance products like car, two-wheeler, and three-wheeler insurance. Which of these
car insurance companies do you like the most?
Please mention it in the comments. If you're
new to the channel, please subscribe to the channel and
like the video. Number four:
Ekko General Insurance
Limited. The parent company of this company is Ekko
Technology and Services Private Limited. This
company was started by Varun Dua.
Its headquarters is
located in Bangalore. The company was started in 2016
and it offers excellent
comprehensively personalized car
insurance.  It provides plans. If you are
new to this channel, then you must subscribe to the channel,
like the video and
share it with your friends.
Number three: HDFC Ergo General
Insurance Company Limited. This company was
started in 2002. Its headquarter
is located in Mumbai and it has
about
122 branches in India and its joint
venture company is HDFC and Ergo International.
Which of these car
insurance companies do you take insurance from,
please mention it in the comments. Number
two: Bajaj Alliance General Insurance
Company Limited. This is a leading insurance
company. Its headquarter is
located in Pune and it was started in 2000
and it
is a company in collaboration with Bajaj Fisher and Alloy AC. Bajaj has a
stakehold of 74% and Alloy has a
hold of 26%. If you are new to this channel, then you
must subscribe to the channel.
Number one: ICICI Lord General
Insurance Company Limited. This company was
started in 2002.  The bank is their parent company
and their headquarter is located in Mumbai. The
company was started in 2001 and their
joint venture is with ISI's Fer Fax A
Financial Holding, which is a Canadian company.
Which of these
companies do you consider to be the top number one and
do mention it in the comments. If you are new to the channel, then do
subscribe to the channel. Thank you for
watching and stay tuned for the next
videos.